http://jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This website is controlled and maintained by Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com, a private company with limited liability incorporated under the laws of the Cyprus.
Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com will hereafter also be referred to as “we” and or “us”. The visitor and/or user of this website will hereafter be referred to as “you”.
By visiting and/or using this website:
you oblige yourself vis-à-vis Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com to use (the content of) this website solely for non-commercial purposes; and
you agree that the terms and conditions as set out in this disclaimer and future versions
hereof apply to you; and you declare that you have read the content of this disclaimer;
you agree that we process your personal information that you provide to us on this website.
Nature of the website
Use of this website is free. This website contains information about and hyperlinks to websites of third parties and is consequently solely informative in nature. No agreement of assignment and/or sale comes into being between you and us, unless this you and us explicitly agree otherwise in writing and/or electronically, like in the event you purchase items via Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com using your Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com credits or if you purchase Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com credits with your credit card, in which event we enter into a purchase agreement with you. This disclaimer also applies to purchase agreement as much as possible.
Privacy
If we acquire personal information of you, we shall process these in a proper and careful manner and in accordance with the Privacy Policy. Please contact the webmaster for questions about the processing of personal information.
Intellectual property rights
In composing (the information and/or content on) this website we endeavor to our best ability to prevent that (the information and/or content on) this website or parts thereof infringe(s) third party intellectual property rights. Nevertheless, if you think that (the information and/or content on) this website or parts thereof infringe(s) your intellectual property rights, you should notify the webmaster within one month after discovery thereof. After one month after such a discovery, your rights and/or title thereto shall be deemed to be waived.
No guarantees
Without being obliged to do so, we endeavor to continuously maintain and update this website. However, we do not guarantee that the information and/or content of (parts of) this website is accurate, complete and/or accessible. The information and/or content of (parts of) this website may be changed or deleted at any moment, without prior notification. You use the information and/or content of (parts of) this website for your own account and risk and indemnify us on our first demand against whatever (third party) claims and/or liabilities that may derive from your use of the information and/or content of (parts of) this website.
This website contains hyperlinks to websites of third parties. Also it may be that website of third parties contain hyperlinks to this website. We exercise the most possible care in selecting the information and/or content that is placed on this website, and, in the selection of third party websites that contain links to this website. However, we do not guarantee that mentioned websites are accurate, complete, accessible and/or in compliance with all applicable laws and regulations. Also, we do not necessarily approve the information and/or content of (parts of) third party websites.
No liability
Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com, its managing directors and/or personnel are, as far as may be disclaimed under applicable law, not liable for damages of whatever nature (including but not limited to damage caused by viruses), that may in whatever manner result from (the use of) the information and/or content on and/or the (im)possibility to acquire access to i) this website; ii) websites of third parties that contain hyperlinks to this website; and iii) websites of third parties where hyperlinks on this website lead to. The burden of proof of any liability rests solely and completely on the user of the website. All claims for damages that the user of the websites claims to have suffered, lapse after 12 months after the allegedly harmful event has occurred. After 12 month the user shall be deemed to have waived its right of action in that respect.
Miscellaneous
If a (part of a) provision in this disclaimer is void or unenforceable the provision in question shall be replaced by a provision that is valid and/or enforceable and corresponds with the void and/or unenforceable provision as close as possible.
This disclaimer and the use of (information and/or the content on) this website is governed by the laws of the Netherlands. All disputes arising here from shall exclusively be brought before the competent court in Cyprus.
Special provisions regarding purchase contracts
If we enter into a purchase agreement with you the following conditions apply:
We will exercise the utmost care in the receipt and delivery of our orders. The address of delivery shall be the address that you have provided us with. We will execute accepted orders as soon as possible though ultimately within 30 days after receipt of the order. The actual delivery date however depends on the transporter.
We will inform you in the event delivery of an ordered product is impossible. We will make an utmost effort to provide you with an alternative item. If there is no alternative available you can dissolve the purchase agreement. In the event a purchase agreement is dissolved, for whatever reason, we will meet our obligation to undo by reimbursing the number of Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com credits you have paid for the item in question. Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com cannot be held liable for damages of whatever nature that results from a purchase agreement that we have entered into with you, unless the damage is caused intentionally or by virtue of cautious recklessness of the management of Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com, or the damage cannot be excluded by Cyprus mandatory (case) law. If you have complaints about an order or the execution of an agreement, please contact our webmaster.
Your Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com credits will be added to your account after your transaction has been approved. Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com credits have no cash value and are non refundable.
Jenna-jameson.datingpersonalsweb.com
Comments are closed.
Search
Search for:
Don't forget to bookmark Jenna Jameson 2019,
All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy - Terms of Service
18 U.S.C. 2257
